http://www.westinautomotive.com/privacy-policy

X
Select Your Vehicle
Select Year
Select Year
202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965
Select Make
Select Make
Select Model
Select Model
Go
Clear
Videos
Product VideosEvent VideosInstallation Videos
Products
New ProductsNerf Step Bars & Running BoardsHitch StepsGrille Guards & GrillesBull BarsSuperwinch Winches & Winch MountsLED LightingJeep Wrangler & Gladiator ProductsBumpersCargo ManagementTool BoxesBody Trim ProductsTowingFloor & Cargo Liners
Where To Buy
Support
Contact UsMy AccountDealer PortalComing Soon2020 Application GuideCatalogsWarranty PolicyUMAP PolicyPrivacy Policy
HomeSupportPrivacy Policy
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy governs the use of your Personal Information (as defined below) by any Websites or mobile Websites owned or operated by Westin Automotive Products, Inc., including the web Website currently located at www.westinautomotive.com (the "Website"), and any other applications, interactive features, widgets and resources offered by Westin through traditional Internet Websites, mobile devices or other platforms (all of which are collectively referred to as the (“Service”). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences, including opting out of certain uses of your Personal Information.
Managing Your Information Preferences
If you want to opt out of having your Personal Information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please let us know by sending us an email at marketing@westinautomotive.com. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically state that you do not want your Personal Information shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.Similarly, if you would like to ask questions or provide comments regarding this Privacy Policy you may do so by sending us an email at customerservice@westinautomotive.comWith respect to communications from us, you may opt-out of our non-transactional emails via a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages. Alternatively, you may email customerservice@westinautomotive.com at any time and ask to be removed.We may continue to send you certain transaction email communications (e.g., emails regarding account notifications, purchases, billings, shipments, returns, customer support questions and similar information regarding your use of the Website and Services).Information which We Collect
Personal Information
We collect information that you provide which may personally identify you, such as your name, address, zip code, credit card number, telephone number, e-mail address, and other personally identifiable information that you choose to provide us with or that you choose to include in your Westin profile or account ("Personal Information"). You may be asked to provide us with personal information when you register on the Website, make a purchase or use any of our Services, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to make purchases or use some or all of the features of the Website or Services.Usage Data and Website Activity
We automatically collect information in connection with the actions you take on the Website ("Usage Data"). For example, each time you use the Website we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Website. This anonymous usage information may be associated with your username and profile, but we do not disclose the associated information to third parties.Cookies and Web Beacons
We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We also may use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a Web Website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Website and Services, such as pre-populating your username for easier login. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Website or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Third-Party Providers and Advertisers (as such terms are defined below), may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.How We Use Information and When We May Share and Disclose Information
Generally
We use Personal Information for internal purposes, such as to provide you with the Website and Services, to improve the Website and Services, to notify you of new products or Services, and to otherwise communicate with you about Westin and information relating to your transactions. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties, including for their direct marketing purposes, without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose to third parties certain Usage Data regarding the Website and Services. However, in such cases, your Usage Data is aggregated with the Usage Data of others and does not identify you individually.Profile Information You Make Available to Others
By using the Website or the Services you may make certain of your Personal Information available to others. For example, if your user name contains your real name, and you post a comment in a public area of the Website, other users may see your name and other information from your public profile that you choose to make available to others, such as your home town. The information you choose to make publicly available may be accessed by users who use the Website or Services and may be accessed by commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo! and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Website.Third-Party Providers
From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who we believe have privacy practices that are consistent with ours ("Third-Party Providers"). For example, we may contract with Third-Party Providers to provide certain services, such as order fulfillment, shipping, hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Third-Party Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider is expected to use reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Third-Party Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by Westin.Advertising
We may work with third-party advertisers, search providers and ad networks ("Advertisers"). We do not share Personal Information with Advertisers, although we may share your vehicle information (e.g., type and model of vehicle). We may share anonymous Usage Data and other non-Personal Information with Advertisers. Advertisers may collect and use information about your use of the Website or Services as well as other Web Websites and services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons in order to collect such information. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you. Advertisements may be shown via the Website, the Services, or on third-party Web Websites. You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative Web Website, which offers information about Internet advertising companies and how to opt-out of their information collection.Joint Services
We may provide services jointly with other companies. In some cases, in order to facilitate such services, it may be necessary to share your Personal Information with such other companies. Before we do so, we will identify the partner, present the joint service provider’s privacy policy to you before you use that service, and obtain your permission to share your Personal Information.Third-Party Services and Applications
Through the Website and the Services, you may have the ability to elect to access third-party services and applications, such as Facebook and other social networks. When you do so, you may be able to import information from those other services and applications and share content with those services. Some of those third-party services may also provide us with information from your accounts which may enable us to enhance and personalize your use of the Website and Services (e.g., so that you can follow your Facebook friends’ activity on the Website or Services). If you elect to use such third-party services or applications through the Services, the information you share with such third-party services and applications will be subject to their privacy policies and your privacy settings for such services. You also may be able to control or block such sharing by changing your privacy settings in such services or applications.Other Transfers
We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Westin. If Westin is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our reasonable judgment, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement
Westin cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Westin or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.Sharing Information with Others
Please be aware that whenever you share information on public forums on the Website, that information may be accessed by others. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.Security
Westin recognizes the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we employ reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure and use. We utilize industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software which encrypts the information you input during transmission. While we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Website or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Website or Services, and you do so at your own risk.Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. In addition, we recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.Processing in of Personal Information
Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States with the exception of EU visitors which is outlined in detail below. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Website or Services, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.
We process your personal information to operate, provide, and improve service that we offer our customers. These purposes include:
Purchase and delivery of products. We use your personal information to take and handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, and communicate with you about orders, products services, and promotional offers.
Provide, troubleshoot, and improve Westin Services. We use your personal information to provide functionality, analyze performance, fix errors, and improve usability and effectiveness of our Website.
Recommendations and personalization. We use your personal information to recommend features, products, and services that might be of interest to you, identify your preferences, and personalize your experience with Westin.
Communicate with you. We use your personal information to communicate with you in relation to Westin purchases or inquiries (e.g., by phone, email, chat).
We use your personal information to display interest-based ads for features, products, and services that might be of interest to you.
Fraud Prevention and Credit Risks. We process personal information to prevent and detect fraud and abuse in order to protect the security of our customers. We may also use scoring methods to assess and manage credit risks.
EU Residents and Website Visitors
If you are a resident or Website visitor located in the European Union (“EU”), United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you are entitled to rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) with respect to your personal data. Westin does not conduct business or track personal data from those visitors that are identified as EU visitors. Collection of personal data on the Website is disabled for visitors from the EU.
Privacy Policy Changes
From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Website or Services constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
X
X
Or
Select VehicleSearch by ProductSearch by Brand
Select Year
Select Year
202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965
Select Make
Select Make
Select Model
Select Model
Go
Clear
New ProductsNerf Step Bars & Running BoardsHitch StepsGrille Guards & GrillesBull BarsSuperwinch Winches & Winch MountsLED LightingJeep Wrangler & Gladiator ProductsBumpersCargo ManagementTool BoxesBody Trim ProductsTowingFloor & Cargo Liners
WestinFEYBruteSuperwinch
×
"fast cache""site_page_cache active""USE CACHE:table""Cached Page"
